[Music]
Uh-huh. Uh-huh. Maybe I'm just trying to
crack it.
Uh-huh. Uh-huh. Baby.
>> And I told her I don't discriminate. I
love a neurodivergent. Don't care if
it's ADHD or the tism. Long as the head
working. If she too much, I do not
judge. Your body is te you serving. I
don't care if the gears in the head
ain't turning 10 in the face. You okay?
Don't care if you get so little bit sick
cuz I'm down for the syndrome. Oh, they
calling you sp baby. Me too. Guess both
of us mentor. Uh-huh. I don't care about
your pronoun. She heard they still
trying to hit though. And she tell me
that she got anxiety. So I'm still
trying to hit.
>> Oh my god.
>> So big. Throw it back. Back back back.
Yeah. Big throw it back.
>> Like throw it back.
>> Cuz I'm trying to crack crack. Yeah. I'm
trying to crack.
>> Yeah. I'm trying to crack.
>> If you turn in the face and thinking
waste, I'm trying to catch
>> and I'm trying to I don't care if you
crazy. If you a baddy, I'm trying to
crack.
>> And she scared to get judged. Baby, I
don't give a [ __ ] If they hate, they
can taste B on my nuts. I don't care for
them regular hoods. And shorty told me
she got ADD. That mean her ass got the
dump. And I told her hop by Pol Express.
Baby, I just want to bust and I need a
Barbie up in that head like Harley cuz I
love me a Y boy. They be the baddest
boring. Sorry. Oh, the face valid body
valid valid. Got it. If the body is 10,
I'm harded. I do not care at the shy.
Damn.
head. Well, baby, I'm sp too. I've been
labeled as problematic. Few schools lose.
They was calling me special. As a kid,
they going to say I was sick. Now they
call me a genius when I make their head
move. So baby, if you on a spectrum,
tell me what you trying to do.
And I told her I don't discriminate. I
love a neuro divergent. Don't care if
it's ADHD or the tism. Long as the head
working. If she y too much, I do not
judge. If body is t you serving. I don't
care if the gears in the head ain't
turning. Turn in the face. You perfect.
I don't care if it's ADHD, if it's ADD,
or it's A2Z. The face on the face and a
cake. Got a little shake to it. You a
great freak. She say she a little
autistic, babe. But I may Okay. If the
brain going to tweak her, I'm game. Stop
playing with me. If the kitty on a plate,
I'll eat. So, throw it back back. Yeah,
big throw it back. Like, throw it back.
>> Cuz I'm trying to crack crack. Yeah,
I'm trying to crack.
>> Yeah, I'm trying to crack.
>> If you turning the face and thinking of
wasting, I'm trying to catch you and I'm
trying to b I don't care if you crazy, if
you a baddie. I'm trying to crack.
[Music]